searchenginecollege.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy | Search Engine College

**PRIVACY POLICY**

We have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.

What information do we collect?

**1\. Access Log Information:**

Google Analytics is used to analyse traffic to this web site. Google Analytics does not create individual profiles for visitors. Unlike some tracking services Google Analytics does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor. Google Analytics only collects aggregate data such as pages viewed, browser used etc. For more information about the Google Analytics privacy policy, please click here.

**2\. Customer Information:**

When you register with our site or purchase products or services from us, we collect information to help us fulfill your request. This information includes your name, address, URL, email address and if you provide it, your telephone number. This information is only used by our staff.

**How do you store my personal information?**

Your information is held in electronic form in our secure databases. We take the strictest precautions to ensure the security of that information.

**Do you store my credit card information?**

We use Swipe HQ (Auckland, New Zealand) and 2Checkout (Ohio, USA) as our merchant payment gateways for customer purchases. Your credit card information will only be stored by our payment gateway partners if you agree to this option during the checkout process. Swipe HQ and 2Checkout both follow strict security procedures to ensure your private information is stored as securely as possible.

**Why did I receive an email from you?**

If you received a mailing from us, either (a) your email address is listed with us as someone who has expressly shared their address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us, or (c) you have requested more information via our web site. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings and giving you the ability to opt-out at any time.

**How do you protect my privacy?**

We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.

**Sharing and Usage**

We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with a third party unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you email based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing agreed services to you.

**How can I stop receiving email from you?**

Every email sent to you from us should contain an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email. Usually this is in the form of a *unsubscribe* link.

If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via our company or purporting to be sent from us, please [contact us](http://www.searchenginecollege.com/contact-us/) as soon as possible so we can deal with it swiftly.
